

ABOUT ME

An active student of Bina Nusantara University pursuing a bachelor's degree focusing on Computer Science. Have experience as web developer who is now active in BINUS IT Division as Associate Member. Have high motivation and high willingness to learn, especially things related to computer science.

SKILL

Laravel
ASP.NET

SQL

Javascript

HTML & CSS

PHP

C#

CONTACT ME

Address

BTN Taman Kenari Blok A 3/9 Bogor, Jawa Barat

Phone

+6282213873139

Email

i.duta@binus.ac.id

Website

https://iamputud.com/

Linkedin

https://linkedin.com/in/iputugedepramaduta/

Github

https://github.com/putuduta

I PUTU GEDE PRAMA DUTA

PROGRAMMER

EXPERIENCE

Associate Member - Part Time

Bina Nusantara IT Division | Mar 2021 - present

 Part of the Software Solution Group 3 Cluster 2 which is responsible for applications development in the Binus Corp website. Learning & Dev., Knowledge Management, and Binus Square.

Assistant Manager of Information Technology Division - 28th BNEC Presidency

BINUS English Club | Mar 2021 - Present

- Assist the Manager to lead 4 IT staff.
- Help develop and maintain a website for the organization.
- Provide training to staff in developing website applications using Laravel.

Staff of Information Technology Division - 27th BNEC Presidency

BINUS English Club | Mar 2020 - Mar 2021

- Create, develop and maintain BNEC Website, Such as Social Event Website, Recruitment Website and Asian English Olympics Website.
- Learn how to develop a website with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, and Laravel Framework.

Mentor Scholarship

BINUS University | Oct 2020 - Jul 2021

- Received scholarship from Binus Student Club & Activity Centre.
- Help and guide other students who have poor grades and difficulty learning a certain subject.

Freshman Leader & Freshman Partner

BINUS University | Jul 2020 - Jul 2021

- Welcome new students and assist the new students in social transition.
- Accompanying the freshmen during the adaptation period of the first-year lectures.

EDUCATION

BINUS UNIVERSITY

2019 - 2023 | Bachelor's degree Computer Science